# **NEHA GHORAD**

SENIOR CORPORATE MANAGER MD OFFICE



#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Certified scrum master and a dynamic management professional with excellent communication skills, focus and determination with an experience of 13+ years. Qualified MBA(Marketing) and BE (IT) with flair for corporate communication, stakeholder management, client communication, strategy & project management.

Looking for positions focusing on corporate operations management, performance dashboard reporting, collaborative communications with various departments and deliverables tracking with focus on prioritisation.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Smartmeters Technologies Pvt Ltd
Sr Manager - Corporate management MD office | Mar'22-present

- Conduct day-to-day project/business coordination across multiple cross functional teams
- Schedule discussions focusing collaboration of departments for issue resolution
- Summarising functional and technical deliverables and tracking till closure of the action items
- Conducting weekly departmental reviews for the monthly goals and publishing weekly dashboard summary on progress to the management
- Aligning the team to the yearly goals, with further identification on the quarterly and monthly goals for tracking and reporting.
- Publishing weekly, monthly and quarterly performance dashboards
- Preparing steering committee presentations
- Reviewing and tracing the manufacturing plant site project and sharing progress summary
- Tracking Production, Sales, RnD and HR discussions and aliging the management discussions with respective team heads aiming priority and urgency
- Maintaining highest level of integrity while dealing with sensitive information

### PREVIOUS ORGANISATIONS SUMMARY

Jekson Vision | Dy Manager -MD Office| 2018-2022 Elsner Technologies | Key account manager| 2016-2017 iGATE| Sr Engineer V&V | 2010-2013

#### SKILLS SUMMARY

- Executive support
- Strategic alignment & reporting
- Team communications
- Dashboard reporting
- Tracking actionable & monitoring
- Presentation & delivery
- Process Improvement

## **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION**

- Master in Business administration -Marketing & project management (2014-2016)
- Bachelor of Engineering
  -Information Technology
  (2005-2009)

#### CERTIFICATIONS

- Scrum Master
- ISTQB- Software Testing
- Hubspot: Inbound Marketing
- Diploma-Cyber Law & Info Security
- MDP Key account management
- MDP World class manufacturing

#### **CONTACT ME AT**



neha.ghorad@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nehaghorad

Ahmedabad, Gujarat